A Guide to the Joseph Francis Fletcher Papers (1931-1991)
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Gift cards to [Thomas H. Hunter] and [Anne Hunter] from Forrest and [Joseph Fletcher], 1986 [December 25], 2 Items (Box-folder 014:129)
- Envelope for Christmas gift to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter?], 1986 December (Box-folder 014:130)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1986 (Box-folder 014:131)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1986 (Box-folder 014:1)
- [Joseph] and Forrest [Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1987 March 5, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:001)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Anne] Hunter, 1987 March 11 (Box-folder 015:002)
- John Fletcher to Joseph Fletcher, 1987 June 17 (Box-folder 015:003)
- Annie [Anne Hunter] to Forrest and [Joseph Fletcher], 1987 October 16 (Box-folder 015:004)
- Forrest and [Joseph] Fletcher to Thomas H. and [Anne] Hunter, 1987 December 16, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:005)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1988 January 25 (Box-folder 015:006)
- Forrest and [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], [1988 February 14] (Box-folder 015:007)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Oscar] Thorup, John Fletcher, [James] Childress, and [Kenneth] Crispell, cc to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1988 February 16 (Box-folder 015:008)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to Thomas H. Hunter, with attached note, 1988 February 20, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:009)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosed essay "On Truth Telling," by Joseph Fletcher, 1988 February 27, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:010)
- Garret Hardin to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1988 March 5, 4 Items (Box-folder 015:011)
- Joseph Fletcher to Garrett [Hardin], 1988 May 8 (Box-folder 015:012)
- Edward W. Hook to Thomas H. Hunter, 1988 May 17 (Box-folder 015:013)
- David Herman to Joseph Fletcher, 1988 June 12 (Box-folder 015:014)
- Forrest and [Joseph] Fletcher to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1988 June 21, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:015)
- Joseph Fletcher to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1988 June 21 (Box-folder 015:016)
- Garrett Hardin to Joseph Fletcher (copy), with attached note by [Fletcher], 1988 June 21, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:017)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1988 June 28 (Box-folder 015:018)
- Editorial from The Hastings Center Report with attached note by [Joseph Fletcher], 1988 June-July (Box-folder 015:019)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1988 July 13, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:020)
- Garrett Hardin to Joe [Joseph Fletcher] (copy), with attached note by [Joseph Fletcher], 1988 July 14 (Box-folder 015:021)
- Esther Morlock to Joseph Fletcher with enclosure: Medical Center Hour Speakers List, 1988 August 8 (Box-folder 015:022)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosure: Garrett Hardin to Joseph Fletcher (copy), 1988 August 11, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:023)
- Joseph Fletcher to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1988 August 13, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:024)
- Joseph Fletcher to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], Joseph Fletcher to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1988 August 15, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:025)
- Joseph Fletcher to Annie [Anne Hunter], 1988 August 31 (Box-folder 015:026)
- Joseph Fletcher to Will Spradlin, 1988 September 10 (Box-folder 015:027)
- Invitation to 60th wedding anniversary party for Forrest and [Joseph] Fletcher, 1988 September 25 (Box-folder 015:028)
- Joseph Fletcher to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1988 October 5 (Box-folder 015:029)
- Garrett Hardin to Joseph Fletcher (copy), 1988 October 5 (Box-folder 015:030)
- Richard Taylor to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1988 October 12, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:031)
- Joseph Fletcher to Garrett [Hardin], with enclosures: Dana B. Copp to Joseph Fletcher; essay by Garrett Hardin (copies), 1988 December 9, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:032)
- Joseph Fletcher to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1988 December 13 (Box-folder 015:033)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1989 January 5 (Box-folder 015:034)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1989 January 18 (Box-folder 015:035)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom and Annie [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1989 January 21 (Box-folder 015:036)
- Medical Record (discharge summary) for Joseph Fletcher, Sarasota Memorial Hospital, 1989 February 18 (Box-folder 015:037)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1989 March 1 (Box-folder 015:038)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1989 March 5 (Box-folder 015:039)
- Sharon Utz Black to Thomas H. Hunter, 1989 March 9 (Box-folder 015:040)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1989 March 11 (Box-folder 015:041)
- J. V. Rajan, request for reprint, 1989 March 28 (Box-folder 015:042)
- Robert C. Nusbaum to Joseph Fletcher], 1989 June 22 (Box-folder 015:043)
- Jim Walters to Joseph Fletcher], with enclosed essay by Walters, 1989 June 22, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:044)
- Joseph Fletcher to Bob [Robert C. Nusbaum], 1989 June 25 (Box-folder 015:045)
- Joseph Fletcher to Jim [Walters], 1989 June 28 (Box-folder 015:046)
- Photocopy of Medical Ethics Advisor vol. 5, no. 8, with attached note from [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1989 August, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:047)
- Copies of poems, 1989 September 10, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:048)
- Joseph Fletcher to Tom and Annie [Thomas H. and Anne Hunter], 1989 October 10 (Box-folder 015:049)
- Joseph Fletcher [Jr.] Memorial Lecture Notice, 1989 November 9 (Box-folder 015:050)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to Thomas H. Hunter, with enclosures, 1989 December 15, 6 Items (Box-folder 015:051)
- Comments by [Joseph Fletcher] on Journal of Pediatrics articles, with a copy of the articles and correspondence, 1989, 8 Items (Box-folder 015:052)
- Joseph Fletcher Bibliography, with attached note of [Joseph Fletcher] to Mary Faith [Marshall], [1989] (Box-folder 015:053)
- Robert J. Geniesse to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1980s?] August 4 (Box-folder 015:054)
- Joseph Fletcher to Annie [Anne] Hunter, 1990 January 23 (Box-folder 015:055)
- Sandy [Schwarz] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1990 February 22 (Box-folder 015:056)
- [Joseph Fletcher] to Thomas [H.] and Ann[e] Hunter, 1990 March 3, 2 Items (Box-folder 015:057)
- Garrett Hardin to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure and note attached from [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1990 May 8, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:058)
- Joseph Fletcher to Tom Thomas [H.] Hunter, 1990 May 31 (Box-folder 015:059)
- Center for Biomedical Ethics Newsletter, with attached note by [Joseph Fletcher], 1990 Summer (Box-folder 015:060)
- Olivia Y. Blakemore to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 June 26 (Box-folder 015:061)
- Christine Martin to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 July 11 (Box-folder 015:062)
- Joseph Fletcher to Cyril Flanagan (copy), with attached note to Thomas [H.] and Ann[e] Hunter, 1990 July 12, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:063)
- Joseph Fletcher to Thomas [H.] and Ann[e] Hunter, with enclosure, 1990 July 24, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:064)
- Garrett Hardin to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 August 25 (Box-folder 015:065)
- Arthur Caplan to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 August 26 (Box-folder 015:066)
- Albert E. Johnson to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1990 August 28, 5 Items (Box-folder 015:067)
- David Alexander to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 August 30 (Box-folder 015:068)
- David C. Thomasma to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 September 7 (Box-folder 015:069)
- Syllabus for U.Va. Religious Studies Course 812, 813, with attached note by [Joseph Fletcher], 1990 Autumn (Box-folder 015:070)
- Ronald E. Cranford to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 September 28 (Box-folder 015:071)
- Raymond Bice to Joseph Fletcher, 1990 October 5 (Box-folder 015:072)
- Joe [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom [Thomas H. Hunter], 1990 December 17 (Box-folder 015:073)
- Joseph Fletcher to [Thomas H. Hunter], with enclosure, 1990 December (Box-folder 015:074)
- Joyce to [Thomas H.] Hunter, with enclosures: obituaries for Joseph Fletcher, 1991 october 30, 3 Items (Box-folder 015:075)
- Obituary for Joseph Fletcher, from the Charlottesville, Virginia "Daily Progress," 1991 October 30 (Box-folder 015:076)
- Materials concerning the memorial service for Joseph Fletcher, 1991 November 9, 4 Items (Box-folder 015:077)
- Les [Lester Kinsolving] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], with enclosure, N.D. (Box-folder 015:078)
- Facsimile of letter of Robert Edward Lee to the Trustees of Washington College, 24 August 1865, N.D. (Box-folder 015:079)
- Society for the Right to Die, form letter drafts, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 015:080)
- Tony to [Joseph Fletcher], N.D. (Box-folder 015:081)
- Chinese Revolution: T. C. Chao to Y. C. and David [Stowe?] (copy), with enclosure, 1948 November 26, 2 Items (Box-folder 016:001)
- Chinese Revolution: Kimber H. K. Den to Joseph Fletcher, 1949 May 12 (Box-folder 016:002)
- Chinese Revolution: T. C. Chao to Joseph Fletcher, with attachment, 1949 June 21, 3 Items (Box-folder 016:003)
- Chinese Revolution: T. C. Chao to Joseph Fletcher, with attachment, 1949 June 25, 3 Items (Box-folder 016:004)
- Chinese Revolution: Lucius C. Porter to Joseph Fletcher, 1949 August 2 (Box-folder 016:005)
- Chinese Revolution: Y. C. to Joseph Fletcher, 1949 August 21 (Box-folder 016:006)
- Chinese Revolution: Lucius C. Porter to Joseph Fletcher, 1949 August 24 (Box-folder 016:007)
- Chinese Revolution: Paul Hutchinson to Joseph Fletcher, 1949 August 26 (Box-folder 016:008)
- Chinese Revolution: Paul Hutchinson to Joseph Fletcher, 1950 August 1 (Box-folder 016:009)
- Chinese Revolution: Dryden L. Phelps to [ ] Melish (copy), 1950 August 1 (Box-folder 016:010)
- Chinese Revolution: K. H. Ting to Joseph Fletcher, 1950 September 5 (Box-folder 016:011)
- Chinese Revolution: Jim Endicott to Joseph Fletcher, 1950 October 10 (Box-folder 016:012)
- Chinese Revolution: Lorna Cheung to Joseph Fletcher, with note by [ ] Roh(?), 1950 October 11 (Box-folder 016:013)
- Chinese Revolution: [ ] Roh(?) to Joseph Fletcher, 1950 October 16 (Box-folder 016:014)
- Chinese Revolution: Choming Chen to Joseph Fletcher, 1950 October 17 (Box-folder 016:015)
- Chinese Revolution: Ronald Hall to Joseph Fletcher (copy), 1950 October 23 (Box-folder 016:016)
- Chinese Revolution: [ ] to Joseph Fletcher (fragment), 1950 October 24 (Box-folder 016:017)
- Chinese Revolution: Hsiu-Ying and Yung-Ch'un Ts'ai to Friends, 1950 October 30 (Box-folder 016:018)
- Chinese Revolution: Lucius C. Porter to Joseph Fletcher, with attachments, 1950 October, 3 Items (Box-folder 016:019)
- Chinese Revolution: Ts'ai to Joseph Fletcher, with note concerning response, 1951 September 9 (Box-folder 016:020)
- Churchman: The Churchman editorials, by Joseph Fletcher?, 1968 November (Box-folder 016:021)
- Churchman: [Thomas K. Thompson] to Edna Ruth Johnson and Joseph Fletcher, 1969 March 3 (Box-folder 016:022)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to Forrest and [Joseph Fletcher], with enclosure, 1969 March 8, 2 Items (Box-folder 016:023)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 March 15 (Box-folder 016:024)
- Churchman: Thomas K. Thompson to [Edna Ruth Johnson] and [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 March 16 (Box-folder 016:025)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 March 21 (Box-folder 016:026)
- Churchman: Edward I. Swanson to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 March 25 (Box-folder 016:027)
- Churchman: Thomas K. Thompson to [Edna Ruth Johnson] and [Joseph Fletchr], 1969 March 27 (Box-folder 016:028)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Thomas K. Thompson] and [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 March 31 (Box-folder 016:029)
- Churchman: Masthead from The Churchman, 1969 March (Box-folder 016:030)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to Joseph Fletcher, 1969 April 2 (Box-folder 016:031)
- Churchman: [Joseph Fletcher] to [Edna Ruth Johnson] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 April 4 (Box-folder 016:032)
- Churchman: [Thomas K. Thompson] to [Edna Ruth Johnson] and [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 April 10 (Box-folder 016:033)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Thomas K. Thompson] and [Joseph Fletcher], with enclosure, 1969 April 15, 2 Items (Box-folder 016:034)
- Churchman: Edna Ruth Johnson to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1969 May 27, 4 Items (Box-folder 016:035)
- Churchman: [Joseph Fletcher] to [Edna Ruth Johnson] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 May 31 (Box-folder 016:036)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 June 13, 2 Items (Box-folder 016:037)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 June 23 (Box-folder 016:038)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to Joseph Fletcher, et al, 1969 June 23 (Box-folder 016:039)
- Churchman: Issue of The Churchman, 1969 June-July (Box-folder 016:040)
- Churchman: Thomas K. Thompson to [Edna Ruth Johnson] and [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 July 13 (Box-folder 016:041)
- Churchman: [Thomas K. Thompson] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 August 7 (Box-folder 016:042)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to Joseph Fletcher and Thomas K. Thompson, 1969 August 20 (Box-folder 016:043)
- Churchman: [Joseph Fletcher] to [Edna Ruth Johnson] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 August 24 (Box-folder 016:044)
- Churchman: Form letter from Joseph Fletcher to Churchman Associates, 1969 September 2, 2 Items (Box-folder 016:045)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 September 3 (Box-folder 016:046)
- Churchman: [Thomas K. Thompson] to [Joseph Fletcher] and [Edna Ruth Johnson], 1969 September 8 (Box-folder 016:047)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 September 10 (Box-folder 016:048)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 September 15 (Box-folder 016:049)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 September 19 (Box-folder 016:050)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 October 10 (Box-folder 016:051)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to Forrest and [Joesph Fletcher], 1969 October 20 (Box-folder 016:052)
- Churchman: El Peet to [Joseph Fletcher], [1969] October 21 (Box-folder 016:053)
- Churchman: Issue of The Churchman, 1969 October (Box-folder 016:054)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1969 November 5 (Box-folder 016:055)
- Churchman: [Thomas K. Thompson] to [Edna Ruth Johnson], 1969 December 7 (Box-folder 016:056)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher] and [Thomas K. Thompson], 1969 December 15 (Box-folder 016:057)
- Churchman: Notes on The Churchman (Box-folder 016:058)
- Churchman: T[homas] K. Thompson to Edna Ruth Johnson, with note by Thompson to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 February 16 (Box-folder 016:059)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher], with enclosure, 1970 May 16, 2 Items (Box-folder 016:060)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 May 20 (Box-folder 016:061)
- Churchman: Mary Gilbert Whaley to Joseph Fletcher, 1970 May 20 (Box-folder 016:062)
- Churchman: [Edna Ruth Johnson] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1970 June 9 (Box-folder 016:063)
- Churchman: Form letter draft from Joseph Fletcher to Churchman Associates, with original versions and final versions, [1970], 7 Items (Box-folder 016:064)
- Ethical Issues (Business Ethics): a special collection of correspondence, notes, case studies, and other documents related to the Kennedy Administration Commission on Business Ethics, 1946-1962 October 16, 44 Items (Box-folder 016:065)
- Ethical Issues (Business Ethics): a special collection of correspondence, notes, case studies, and other documents related to the Kennedy Administration Commission on Business Ethics, 1962 November 8-1963, N.D., 53 Items (Box-folder 016:066)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of notes, newspaper clippings, and other materials on various political, social and religious issues, 1943 September 5-1956 June, N.D., 89 Items (Box-folder 017:001)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of newspaper clippings, pamphlets, notes, and essays on various ethical issues, 1949-1961, 125 Items (Box-folder 017:002)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of newspaper clippings, pamphlets, notes, case studies and essays principally concerning euthanasia and other medical ethical issues, 1951-1961, 99 Items (Box-folder 017:003)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of newspaper clippings, notes, a pamphlet, case studies, essays and a reprint on various ethical issues, 1955-1961, 61 Items (Box-folder 017:004)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of newspaper clippings, pamphlets, newsletters, and notes on birth control and other ethical issues, 1955-1965, N.D., 69 Items (Box-folder 017:005)
- Ethical Issues: case studies of ethical problems and a syllabus for the course "Problems of Conscience for the Pastor" by Joseph Fletcher, [1959], 16 Items (Box-folder 017:006)
- Ethical Issues: ethical case studies, 1960 January-1965 April 28, N.D., 45 Items (Box-folder 018:001)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of notes, newspaper clippings, and other materials on problems of conscience, 1960 April 7-1961 June 17, N.D., 131 Items (Box-folder 018:002)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of case studies, reprints, notes, newspaper clippings, and correspondence concerning various ethical issues, 1968-1986, 35 Items (Box-folder 018:003)
- Ethical Issues: notes and other materials on ethical case studies and questions, [1970s], 49 Items (Box-folder 018:004)
- Ethical Issues: special collection of materials on population, pregnancy, and related issues, including the essay "Birth Control: A New Dimension," by Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 51 Items (Box-folder 018:005)
- Financial: miscellaneous financial materials, [1940]-1991 January 27, N.D., 19 Items (Box-folder 018:006)
- Financial: royalty agreements and other materials concerning publications, 1946 October 1-1970 January 5, 9 Items (Box-folder 018:007)
- Financial: receipts, bills, and other materials related to medical care, 1950 February 10-1970 May 8, N.D., 16 Items (Box-folder 018:008)
- Financial: materials and correspondence concerning the Episcopal Church pension fund, Social Security, and retirement, 1952 January-1970 June 11, N.D., 23 Items (Box-folder 018:009)
- Financial: leases, 1956 May 7-1960 November 19, 2 Items (Box-folder 018:010)
- Financial: insurance policies (automobile and homeowners), with related correspondence and notes, 1966 December 6-1970 May 16, 14 Items (Box-folder 018:011)
- Financial: assignment of copyright and related documents, 1968 May 15, 3 Items (Box-folder 018:012)
- Financial: correspondence and other materials related to purchase of house at 52 Van Ness Road, Belmont, Mass., 1968 November 1-1969 September 2, N.D., 16 Items (Box-folder 018:013)
- Financial: furnace service guarantee for 52 Van Ness Road, Belmont, Mass., 1969 February 18 (Box-folder 018:014)
- Financial: bill for legal services regarding purchase of 52 Van Ness Road, Belmont, Mass., 1969 April 23 (Box-folder 018:015)
- Financial: payroll record for Joseph Fletcher, Episcopal Theological School, 1969 June 12 (Box-folder 018:016)
- Financial: materials concerning move of furniture from Massachusetts to New York, 1969 October 16-December 1, 12 Items (Box-folder 018:017)
- Financial: statement of account for royalties on German edition of Situation Ethics, 1969 October 20 (Box-folder 018:018)
- Financial: notes concerning Kittredge finances, [1960s], 3 Items (Box-folder 018:019)
- Financial: sample lease with attached note by [Joseph Fletcher], [1980s], 2 Items (Box-folder 018:020)
- Humor: humor, 1951 December 6-1960 December 5, N.D., 29 Items (Box-folder 018:021)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, no pagination, no corrections, 1989 April 30, May 1, early May, June 23, July 2 (Box-folder 018:022)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, with pagination and autograph corrections, pp. 1-54, 1989 April 30, May 1, early May, June 23, July 2 (Box-folder 018:023)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall. [Cataloguer's note: transcript pages 55-368 were not included in the Fletcher Papers donation.] 1989 (Box-folder 019:001)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 369-410, 1989 November 11 (Box-folder 019:002)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 411-458, 1989 December 3 (Box-folder 019:003)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 459-507, 1989 December 21 (Box-folder 019:004)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 508-604, 1989 December 31 (Box-folder 019:005)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 605-656, 1990 January 20 (Box-folder 019:006)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 657-706, 1990 February 3 (Box-folder 019:007)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 707-709, 1990 February 10 (Box-folder 019:009)
- Interview Transcripts: Joseph Fletcher with Mary Faith Marshall, pp. 710-721, 1990 February 18 (Box-folder 019:009)
- Interview Transcripts: notes of a conversation with [Joseph Fletcher] by [Mary Faith Marshall], [1990] June 14 (Box-folder 019:010)
- Interview Transcripts: Elizabeth to Mary Faith Marshall, [1990], 2 Items (Box-folder 019:011)
- Lectures: radio address by Joseph Fletcher, "Mr. Coughlin," 1939 August 6 (Box-folder 019:012)
- Lectures: "Dialectical Materialism and a Theological Comment," Joseph Fletcher, 1943 October (Box-folder 019:013)
- Lectures: "Six Propositions: the New Look in Christian Ethics," (drafts) Joseph Fletcher, 1959 April 30, 2 Items (Box-folder 019:014)
- Lectures: "Lecture I: Prolegomenon and One Proposition," "Lecture II: Four More Propositions," "Lecture III: One Proposition and an Epilogue," Joseph Fletcher, 1963, 3 Items (Box-folder 019:015)
- Lectures: Canterbury Lectures "The Strategy of the Christian Love Ethic," and "What Does It Mean to be Good?," Joseph Fletcher, 1965 October 17, 2 Items (Box-folder 019:015a)
- Lectures: excerpts from Joseph Fletcher's address at the Fourth Annual Conference on Family Life, St. Louis, Mo., 1965 December 1 (Box-folder 019:016)
- Lectures: "Deciding What is Right," Joseph Fletcher, 1976 June 4 (Box-folder 019:017)
- Lectures: "Justice: Moral Mathematics," Joseph Fletcher, 1980 March 26 (Box-folder 019:018)
- Lectures: "Odyssey: From Theology to Humanism," Joseph Fletcher, [also includes a draft with revisions for publication?] 1980, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 019:019)
- Lectures: "Humanism and Theism in American Ethics," Joseph Fletcher, 1981 February 18 (Box-folder 019:020)
- Lectures: "Science = Control," Joseph Fletcher, 1981 September 18 (Box-folder 019:021)
- Lectures: "Professional Jedgment: Ideals and Realities," Joseph Fletcher, 1985 April 12-13 (Box-folder 019:022)
- Lectures: "Recollections and Reflections: Biomedical Ethics," "Recollections and Reflections: Clinical Pastoral Education," Joseph Fletcher, [includes conference brochure], 1986 March 13-16, 3 Items (Box-folder 019:023)
- Lectures: Harvard Club address by Joseph Fletcher, with note by [Joseph Fletcher] and newspaper clipping copy, 1986 December 9, 3 Items (Box-folder 019:024)
- Lectures: A.B.A. speach [title lost, missing pages 1 and 2], Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 019:025)
- Lectures: "Behavior Control: Is It Ethical?" Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 019:026)
- Lectures: "The Case for Abortion: A Problem of Individual Ethics and Public Policy," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 019:027)
- Lectures: "Comprehension: A World View for Science, or, How to Keep from Being an Idiot," with several drafts, Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 4 Items (Box-folder 019:028)
- Lectures: course lecture 1 (3 parts), "The Point of View," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 019:029)
- Lectures: course lecture 2 (3 parts) [part 1 incomplete], "Ethics in General," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 019:030)
- Lectures: course lecture 3 (2 parts), "Theological Bases," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 019:031)